[
  {
    "question": "What is the syntax to output text in console in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "console.write('Hello World')",
      "console.log('Hello World')",
      "print('Hello World')",
      "printf('Hello World')"
    ],
    "answer": "console.log('Hello World')"
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you declare an integer variable 'x' with a value of 5 in C++?",
    "options": ["int x = 5;", "x = 5;", "x := 5;", "Int x = 5;"],
    "answer": "int x = 5;"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a loop structure in C++?",
    "options": ["for", "while", "do-while", "repeat-until"],
    "answer": "repeat-until"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Python data type is an ordered sequence of items?",
    "options": ["List", "Tuple", "Dictionary", "Set"],
    "answer": "List"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you indicate the end of a block of code in Python?",
    "options": [
      "With a semicolon (;)",
      "With a closing bracket (})",
      "With the keyword 'end'",
      "With indentation"
    ],
    "answer": "With indentation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a way to create a comment in a JavaScript program?",
    "options": [
      "<!-- This is a comment -->",
      "# This is a comment",
      "/* This is a comment */",
      "COMMENT: This is a comment"
    ],
    "answer": "/* This is a comment */"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct operator to compare two variables for equality in JavaScript?",
    "options": ["==", "===", "=", "!="],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "question": "What HTML tag is used to insert JavaScript code into a webpage?",
    "options": ["<java>", "<js>", "<script>", "<javascript>"],
    "answer": "<script>"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the 'www' stand for in a URL?",
    "options": [
      "World Wide Wait",
      "World Wide Web",
      "World Wide Words",
      "World With Web"
    ],
    "answer": "World Wide Web"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'GUI' stand for in computer science?",
    "options": [
      "Graphic User Interface",
      "Graphical Unifying Interface",
      "Graphical User Interface",
      "Generic User Interface"
    ],
    "answer": "Graphical User Interface"
  }
]
